A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Special Studies Project, RG 4 FA387
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Special Studies Project, 1956-1964; 4; 28 Cubic Feet 70 boxes
  - Office Reference and Report Publication Files, 1956-1960; J; 5 Cubic Feet 12 boxes
    - Subpanel IV - Published Background Material (Box 64, Folder 695)
    - Subpanel IV Report - Final Draft, 1958 (Box 65, Folder 696)
    - Papers V-1 through V-9 (Box 65, Folder 697)
    - Subpanel V - Draft Report (Box 65, Folder 698)
    - Subpanel V - Published Background Material (Box 65, Folder 699)
    - Papers VI-1 through VI-6 (Box 66, Folder 700)
    - Papers VI-7 through VI-12 - Bundy Paper (Box 66, Folder 701)
    - Subpanel VI - Draft Report - Nelson Rockefeller Copy (Box 66, Folder 702)
    - Subpanel VII - Documents - Nelson Rockefeller Copies (Box 66, Folder 703)
    - Overall Panel - Final Report Outline - Nelson Rockefeller Copy, 1957 June 19 (Box 67, Folder 704)
    - Overall Panel - Report Comments - Nelson Rockefeller Copy, 1957 March 19-20 (Box 67, Folder 705)
    - Overall Panel Meeting - Summary of Subpanel Work, 1957 March 19-20 (Box 67, Folder 706)
    - Editorial Committee Meeting - Nelson Rockefeller Copy, 1957 September 16 (Box 67, Folder 707)
    - Publications Committee - Nelson Rockefeller Copy, 1957 September 15 (Box 67, Folder 708)
    - Subpanel I - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1956 November - 1957 April (Box 67, Folder 709)
    - Subpanel II - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1956 November - 1957 March (Box 67, Folder 710)
    - Subpanel III - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1956 December - 1957 February (Box 67, Folder 711)
    - Subpanel IV - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1957 January-April (Box 68, Folder 712)
    - Subpanel V - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1957 January-April (Box 68, Folder 713)
    - Subpanel VI - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1956 November - 1957 May (Box 68, Folder 714)
    - "Prospect for America: The Rockefeller Panel Reports" - Correspondence, 1960 September - 1961 April, undated (Box 68, Folder 715)
  - Special Formats, K (Reel Recording "Challenge to America: Economic and Social Aspects" program)
    - Audio (Reel Recording "Challenge to America: Economic and Social Aspects" program, Reel Recording of "The Power of Democratic Ideas", Reel Recording from "Pursuit of Excellent and Education" and " The Future" programs)
    - Published material (Volume Published book "Processed for America The Rockefeller Panel Reports")